All right, guys. We are about to enter
Today is my first day of sophomore year.
>> Here we go again.
>> We'll start off with the first day of
school morning routine, slowly but
surely make our way to the campus where
we tell you about everything that
happened today. Stay till the end to
find out how it went.
Good morning. It is currently 5:09,
August 12th. It is the first day of
sophomore year. I promise you I stayed
up until 1:00 just laying in bed trying
to sleep. It was so bad.
Not doing like the normal like back to
school glow up was kind of different.
Can we talk about how adorable these
are? They're first nails. Let's get
ready for the first day of sophomore
year. Guys, so I rearranged my room for
school and basically
I woke up and my camera didn't charge in
the night. Guys, I've been charging this
camera for 2 days. We'll go on from
here.
I just brushed my teeth and now I'm
going to go ice my face to wake up a
little bit more and get rid of the
puffiness like right here.
Ooh, this might be harder than I
remember.
Sometimes I regret the day I put this
ring on. Bring me a little water now.
I'm thirsty.
Girlfriend, I love the feeling of waking
up before the rest of the world. Comment
down below if you're a morning person or
if you're a night person. I think I'm a
morning, but specifically like 5:00 a.m.
Next, I'm going to go take a shower and
like do my curls and then I'm going to
define them in my room. The rose gold.
Ooh, yeah. Mhm.
Oh, that wasn't bad. That was not bad at
all. Time to get ready. I'm trying to
figure out where I want the camera.
So, basically, I just ripped my PJs.
Yeah, but I have good news and I have
bad news. The good news, it's not the
butt crack. The bad news, obviously I
was like putting my arm into the shirt
and then it just ripped. And normally it
doesn't do that.
Here we go again. A year later and my
sister's freaking alarm is going off.
It's not just a normal alarm. It's the
one where it like wakes you up slowly.
She's not even here. She is on a flight
to Missouri right now. Who's she waking
up? The whole house.
Okay, I'm actually getting a little bit
more excited.
As I am classic leave-in conditioner.
This is the magic ingredient for my
hair.
This is kind of a new thing where I just
brush it through rather than like
squeezing it. So, I hope I'm not like
ruining the curls. I have faith they'll
turn out good though.
Basically, you brush the curls forward
and then you start folding at the end
and then you flip your hair back. The
hair might actually eat down today. And
now I'm going to do my skin care. First,
I go in with CeraVe. CeraVe is like the
best moisturizer for your skin.
It's 6:24 right now.
25, but I'm doing pretty good on time.
Do you guys know the audio where it's
like You're not getting it. It's not
clocking to you. It's not clocking to
you that I'm standing on business, is
it? It's not clocking to me that it's
the first day of school. It still feels
like summer. Guess who has geometry
first semester?
Guess who has chemistry first period?
They're like, let's see if she can
survive every possible class that could
make one crash out. Basically, I'm doing
Merps lash routine. Um my lashes don't
turn out even half as good as hers do,
but they do turn out better ever since I
started doing her routine. It's kind of
funny because you curl it like 15 times.
After you apply your mascara, you go dry
your lashes with a hair dryer.
Don't mind me. I'm going to put on my
jazz.
Mascara is done. Kind of excited for
school, but at the same time not. I wish
I had like two more weeks at least of
summer just because there's been a lot
going on with merch. This month is
definitely going to be testing me,
discipline, and my perseverance. It's
going to be hard managing a business and
doing school, so this will be my first
time doing that. But in honor of 100K, I
promised you guys I would launch merch.
That's basically what I did all summer.
If we have icebreakers today and we're
like, "What did you do for the summer?"
I'm going to be like, "Started my own
business." I didn't travel. I didn't go
out too much because I was always
working, but I did take some time to
hang out with friends. I made new
friends. It was fun. Like the summer was
a good balance of working and a good
balance of just being a kid. So, I have
no regrets. Like I love how I spent the
summer. I know I'm going to look crazy
for a minute. It's like two different
shades, but I have to let it bake and it
will turn out good.
Like I thought I was going to have
career center first semester, but I
actually have it second semester now,
which is fine because I'm so so excited.
AV media production, I believe. That's
the class I chose. It's filmmaking. I
love filmmaking. Like I want to be a
director when I'm older. I have my
vision board right there. That's
something I think a lot of people don't
know because I don't talk about it a lot
in my vlogs, but I'll start talking
about it more. I guess just for a little
life update, I'm working on my first
business right now, which I can announce
the name very soon. I just received my
samples last night. It was so fun. In
the next vlog, you guys are actually
going to see the merch. Make sure you're
watching and staying up-to-date with my
YouTube short. Looks like we're going to
be launching next month in September,
and you guys should be excited, too.
I've been trying to post more on YouTube
shorts. Why do I feel like my camera's
about to die? Oh, no.
I'm going to actually crash out.
Hey,
cutie. Makeup is done. I love it.
Definitely a good makeup day, and it's
going to be even better once my lashes
are dry because I'm going to curl them,
and then they're going to be like,
"Whoa." But now, I'm going to go pack my
lunch. Okay, it is time for one of my
favorite parts of school vlogs. Time to
pack my lunch.
Okay, time for my favorite part, packing
my lunch.
All right, guys, lunch is packed. Let's
do a little lunch haul. I have some
white bread, cucumbers, blackberries,
blueberries, peppered salami, tomatoes,
Cheez-Its, and some strawberries. At
least for the first couple days, maybe
weeks, I'm going to use this lunch box
again, even though it's like low-key
ripped. I was supposed to get a new one,
but I totally forgot.
So, this will have to work. But, that's
why I need to get a new one ASAP. Y'all,
I don't know why my phone just updated,
but I got so scared my phone was not
turning on. That's why it's out of the
case right now. I got scared, but it was
updating for some reason, and I didn't
even like authorize an update. Anyway,
time to give you guys an outfit haul.
Nike socks, because I'm wearing these
like really fashionista boots.
Why did I just describe it like that?
They're just like these gray, kind of
like roughly boots. I know a lot of you
are probably shocked I'm not wearing
Campuses. Red top from Brandy Melville.
It's so adorable. And then this
I just ironed this yesterday. Why is it
so folded? This dark wash denim skirt
from Addicted. For jewelry, I'm going to
wear this necklace. It's from
Francesca's. Look at the details. I feel
like this is going to be my new favorite
necklace. Gold ring drop earrings, some
rings and bracelets. I'll show you. So,
outfit transition, 3 2 1.
Okay, guys, outfit of the day. I'm
low-key going to be late at this point,
but it's okay, cuz we're going to be
fashionably late. This is the outfit
tried on. I'll give y'all a better one
at school later. Yeah, off to school we
go. Hey guys, we are on the way to
school now. I have my oatmeal. Am I
pronouncing that weird? Oatmeal? Did I
say o-meal? You said o-meal. I have my
oatmeal.
Hopefully I'm not late, but I probably
will be because the traffic on the first
day of school at my high school is
actually insane.
Cut the cameras. Happy first day of
school.
All right guys, we are about to enter
The line is so long.
Yeah, but I have to wait in a line to go
to school.
Shoot, I don't even have any friends.
Well, that I can meet up with. Maybe I
do. Let's see. Y'all, the line is
actually crazy because our school added
like weapons detection, so now we have
to wait. All right guys, we are at
school and basically
there's a huge line. Oh yeah, here's
Karen. I met with her in the line. I'm
so happy. I'm going to crash out because
they just told us we need to have our
iPads out, but like literally it's like
crazy.
We're on the main campus officially.
This is our new campus. It almost feels
like freshman year a little bit.
Are you excited?
And your first period is English, right?
I'm not excited either. I'm Wait, I
don't know where I'm going. Look.
Okay, I need to pull out my schedule cuz
I don't know where I'm going. The
officer just asked if I knew where I was
going. I don't know where I'm going.
I hate carrying around a camera on the
first day of school.
But it's fine. Okay, I have to go
upstairs. Bye. I don't know, this could
be one of the only school Look at how
empty it is first of all because
everybody is in the weapons detection.
I'm curious. I'm also out of breath
because
I'm like walking around the school in
heels and I'm upstairs first period, but
I'm looking for my chemistry class.
Yes, I'm literally out of breath. Okay,
I'll I'm probably going to stop vlogging
because like yeah, peace out guys. I'll
see you after first period or in first
period if I feel brave ENOUGH TO VLOG.
OKAY GUYS, I'M HERE WITH SHARINA.
Our classes are right next to each
other, so that's like good news. Um
we're at lunch right now. I was like too
afraid to vlog in the other classes, but
how's your day been going? It's been
going good. I'm really tired.
>> Me too. I feel like entrepreneurship and
like business was tiring. What's your
first period?
>> English. Oh, that's right.
Do you have a little carrots? No, I
don't. I have it. There was a girl in my
business class. Her name was like G Mo.
G Mo? But I accidentally said it as a
Gmail.
That's the senior girl I was like kind
of be friends with.
I'm glad we got here early.
But I still haven't seen anyone we know.
I don't know about you. Oh I
forgot you tonsils.
In a second.
Wait, Sharina, we can twin. I got those.
I bought you them for 30. But I saw your
Instagram post. The shoes were
Oh my god.
You got so many.
One of them my sister and I are sharing.
Okay,
but still so many. You love them. Yeah.
Guys, I'm editing right now, but I need
to do a quick disclaimer. Obviously, you
can see like the pretty part of the
halls, but I did buy it with 95% of that
with my own hard-earned money. You
obviously see the aftermath of like a
shopping spree, but you don't see like
all of the genuine sleepless nights and
like long hours working to be able to
earn the money to afford that stuff. So,
I just want to say I'm very, very
grateful. Make sure you're not comparing
yourselves to things you see on social
media, but you know, make sure you don't
assume anything. But yeah, super
grateful that I'm healthy enough to work
hard enough to earn the things that I
have. I was looking at all these kids
that got bus cuts.
Do you know anyone in your classes with
you?
Literally, the best thing that's
happened is lunch, you know? Yeah. Who
cares about highlights? Yes, I saw her
this morning. We walked together in
weapons detection.
What time did you get here?
Oh, wow. You got here earlier. Tomatoes,
salami, blackberries, blueberries,
cucumbers.
I just burned a piece of bread cuz I
don't know.
If you want anything, JUST
I'LL TAKE IT. I WOKE UP AT 5:30.
I woke up I was like counting. I was
like using methods by like counting
backwards.
I was counting the alphabet backwards. I
couldn't sleep.
I was using methods, too, but it was
just like Alison recommended ASMR, which
I never listened to, but Kind of.
I don't know. I just I just I just
eventually fell asleep. I don't
remember. My brother got home at 1:00,
and he's so loud. He he was talking so
loud with my parents in the living room.
So, then I was like awake, and then I
think I woke up again at 3:00, so it's
kind of crazy.
You had like 3 hours of sleep.
Oh my gosh.
Yeah, low-key.
Thank you.
They are nice.
They're they're press-ons.
This is going to be like note that
Tuesday every day. Oh my gosh.
I low-key have to use the bathroom.
Geometry.
Regular. I'm not good at math. What
about you?
Why did I say it like that?
French?
That's her name. I like your nails. What
the heck? Rihanna did them.
Rihanna's winning.
Nice.
Rihanna joke?
She does nails? I'm going to go to
Rihanna. I knew she did nails cuz last
year I had StuCo with her, and I'd
always be like, "Your nails look so
good." She's like, "I did it myself."
Rihanna, if you're watching this, hit me
up because
Hey vlog, it's Christian. What's up? You
You tell them about your day. Okay.
My day has been quite good. Uh started
off with chem. Chemistry has been like
It was easy.
>> Yeah. I said my teacher kept on talking
about like some syllabus, which was, you
know, boring. Then second period
Oh, you want to say hi? Hi.
I'm like a pro at this. Oh, second
period, I had creative writing, which I
had like Ali and like a lot of friends
in there, which was also good cuz I like
writing, you know. Third is soccer,
that's going to be cool. And then I'm
going to fourth period right now.
>> you do in soccer? Oh, soccer was He
talked about the route.
>> name? My name's Christian. Christian?
Yeah. I'm Sharina. Oh, nice to meet you.
>> knows you from the vlog. Yeah, I'm like
a
>> Yeah.
>> You seen my edits?
But yeah.
Look at us on the main campus. It's
literally so crowded. I'll let you go.
Okay, bye. Bye vlog. Bye.
Hey!
You're so cute.
That looks so good on you. Hey! HAPPY
FIRST DAY.
YOU LOOK SO PRETTY, GRACE.
PEOPLE ARE CATFISH ME CUZ THEY'RE GOING
to think I'm taller than I
No, yeah, you are taller
Like the whole outfit so Yeah, thank
you.
Oh my god, I love your shirt.
You like her schedule? It's fine, no.
How was first semester? It was really
fun.
Guys, it is like 80 No, no, not 80. It's
like 100° outside. I'm burning. Like I'm
burning. Yeah.
And all of the buses are late, so we're
just all stranded out here. This is like
terrible. Are you the same bus? Yeah.
Oh, that's great.
Hello, guys. HOW WAS YOUR FIRST DAY? It
was bad. It was bad. Oh, and it was hot
out here. Really? I know, it's so hot.
How was your first day? It was better
than freshman year. It was better? Yeah.
My classes are pretty good. But my
fourth is actually
All right, guys, we are back home from
jail school. I mean, we're back home
from school and it is time to do the
recap of the first day of sophomore
year. I did this last year for freshman
year. I didn't vlog in any of my classes
today, I think. I don't think I vlog in
a single one just because I'm always
kind of nervous to vlog in my classes on
the first day. I have to like kind of
see if the teacher is strict or chill.
Good news, chemistry, that was actually
pretty good. It was fine. It was like
normal. First period teacher I think is
chill. He seems like a normal teacher to
me. Second period is entrepreneurship. I
think that was my favorite period of the
day just because my teacher is so chill.
I'm excited to network with like-minded
students who are also trying to be
entrepreneurs. I actually made friends
with a senior today. Shout out Gimo if
you're watching this. Entrepreneurship
was probably the most social class of
the day. Like we talked the most. It
seemed like everybody got comfortable
with each other fairly quickly, which is
great sign. The teacher said we're going
to be doing business pitches at some
point in the semester, so I'm curious to
see like how that's going to go. I guess
we're going to have to like present.
When we walked in the room of
entrepreneurship, guess what was on the
board?
Give you some time. It was a picture of
Shark Tank. And so I was like, "Okay, we
are talking business here." Literally.
Third period is principles of business.
One it entrepreneurship and psychology.
I got placed in my alternative. It's
fine. I'll just be all businessed out
this semester, I guess. But I also like
my third period because he's probably
the most chill teacher, I would say.
He's a football coach. You know how
coaches are, right? Like they're just
chill. He brought us candy for answering
questions and it was just really nice.
We had an assignment, but it was super
easy. Okay, and then lunch. Ooh, maybe
that was the best part of the day. I
would say lunch was the best part of the
day. Me and Shrina got there I think too
early low-key, but we got a great table
like by the window. You guys saw. And
then fourth period.
Let's talk about that.
I need a schedule change. This is giving
me flashbacks to last year.
I'm in for some real trouble. Geometry,
guys.
First of all, it's fourth period, so
it's the end of the day. Guys, I fell
asleep in the class. I promise. Overall,
I would say I'm happy with my schedule.
Pretty much everyone I talked with today
said they weren't happy with their
schedule. If you really look at it, my
classes are kind of like boring, but I
always try and have a positive
perspective in every aspect. I stepped
out of my comfort zone today talking
with like upperclassmen. It was a big
change from last year because on the
first day last year, I literally cried.
Why am I bringing this up? It's gone.
Fear's gone. I already have senior
friends which I'm sad to leave. Shoutout
Preesha. If you're watching this,
shoutout. Happy senior year. Bus. Let me
set you the scene, okay? 90° in the
afternoon, high heels, heavy backpack,
stress, crowdedness, overstimulation,
looking for a bus that is 30 minutes
late. It was actually so annoying. Like,
I did see a couple of fine shites, but
I'm not going to That's all I'm going to
say. People watch my vlogs, so
not trying to not trying to
Nope. I'm good. So, the question of the
day is how was your first day of school?
Or, if you haven't gone back to school
yet, are you excited for the first day?
But yeah, today was a great day and I
hope you guys enjoyed watching this
video. If you enjoyed, make sure you
comment the star emoji and I will see
you in the next one. Peace out. Bye.